Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Football: Championship Ring Studio Shots, Recruitment Book Images, 10/2011 CWU vs. WOU Game Photos Fall (Box-folder 42-2)
- Fall Sports; 09/2011 Women's Soccer, 12/2011 Men's Basketball (Box-folder 42-3)
- Miscellaneous Sports: Football #44 Plaque, 12/2011 Men's Basketball, ROTC vs. AFROTC Flag Football, 10/2011 Volleyball (Box-folder 42-4)
- Women's Basketball, 2012- (Box-folder 42-5)
- Volleyball Disc 2: 08/2012 Volleyball, Vs. 10/2012 Walla Walla (Box-folder 42-6)
- Spring Sports: 04/2012 Spike Arlt Track Meet, 04/2012 Softball vs. NNU, 04/2012 Baseball (Box-folder 42-7)
- Men's Basketball: Vs. Walla Walla, 2012- (Box-folder 42-8)
- Women's Soccer, 2012- (Box-folder 42-9)
- Volleyball Disc 1 08/2012 Volleyball, vs. 10/2012 Walla Walla (Box-folder 42-10)
- Soccer, 2013- (Box-folder 42-11)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Volleyball Fall, 2013- (Box-folder 42-12)
- Wildcat Weekend Welcome Football Game Fall, 2013- (Box-folder 42-13)
- Athletics Fall: Basketball Studio Light on Court, 10/2013 Volleyball (Box-folder 42-14)
- Fall Sports: 10/2014 Volleyball, 10/2014 Women's Rugby (Box-folder 42-15)
- Athletics: 01/2014 Men's Basketball, 03/2014 Baseball, 04/2014 Softball (Box-folder 42-16)
- Athletics: 04/2014 Spike Arlt, 02/2014 Women's Basketball (Box-folder 42-17)
- Athletics: Studio Light Athlete Action Shots Disc 3, 2014- (Box-folder 42-18)
- Athletics: Studio Light Athlete Action Shots Disc 4, 2014- (Box-folder 42-19)
- Athletics: Studio Light Athlete Action Shots Disc 2, 2014- (Box-folder 42-20)
- Athletics: Studio Light Athlete Action Shots Disc 1, 2014- (Box-folder 42-21)
- Fall Sports: 12/2014 Women's Basketball, 12/2014 Men's Basketball, 11/2014 Men's Rugby, 10/2014 Soccer (Box-folder 42-22)
- I.T Klemin, 2004- (Box-folder 42-23)
- Papadopoulos: Physical Education Disc 2 01/2004 Mark Oursland Math Class (Box-folder 42-24)
- Steven Verhey: 04/2004 Mint Compost Research (Box-folder 42-25)
- Alan Cant: 06/2004 C.O.B. Professor (Box-folder 42-26)
- 02/2004 Kovalerchuk Computer Science (Box-folder 42-27)
- 03/2004 Lene Pedersen (Box-folder 42-28)
- 06/2004 ChenYang Li, Political Science Professor (Box-folder 42-29)
- Video Game Competitions, no date- (Box-folder 42-30)
- Video Game Competitions, no date- (Box-folder 42-31)
- Franken Glass 1, no date- (Box-folder 42-32)
- Franken Glass 2, no date- (Box-folder 42-33)
- Franken Glass 3, no date- (Box-folder 42-34)
- Rosario Art Jazz in the Valley, 2004- (Box-folder 42-35)
- Post It Shots, 2004- (Box-folder 42-36)
- Homecoming Variety: Alumni memorabilia, Shofard Plaque, 2004- (Box-folder 42-37)
- Events Disc 2: Fireworks Flag Pavilion, 2004- (Box-folder 42-38)
- Events Disc 1: Memorial Day Student Appreciation Day Non-Traditional Students BBQ, 2004- (Box-folder 42-39)
- ESL Students, 2004- (Box-folder 42-40)
- BackUp Disc 2: Chinook Award, Frost, Hydrogen Fuel Cell Unveiling, Sports, King Kummer, 2004- (Box-folder 42-41)
- Headshots: Donors/Alumni, Faculty, 2004- (Box-folder 42-42)
- Headshots: Administration, ASCWU B.O.D., Employee of MO., Graduate Studies, ROTC, Staff, Students, 2004- (Box-folder 42-43)
- Kamola Historical Images: Power poles, Concept Shots, 2003- (Box-folder 42-44)
- Wendy Bohrson with Graduate Students, Seth Mattos, Geology Lab, and Compu. Micro, no date- (Box-folder 42-45)
- International Students Graduates: Wall of Oppression, 2003- (Box-folder 42-46)
- Teaching: D'Aquisto, gee, Kuhlken, Lapsley, Lee, Martin, Madlem, McCutcheon, Miller, Ogden, Palmquist, Physics, Piacsek, Pinkart, Rubin, Sun, Writing Center, 2004- (Box-folder 42-47)
- Student Fun Wildcat Welcome Weekend, 2003- (Box-folder 42-48)
- Featured Students: Disc 1, 2003- (Box-folder 42-49)
- Campus Life Disc-1, 2003- (Box-folder 42-50)
- Bookstore, Centers, Orchesis Heads, OSTC Winnebago, Parking Signs, no date- (Box-folder 42-51)
- Yakima H.E.P. Images (Hispanic), 2003- (Box-folder 42-52)
- CHCI: C.O.B, 2003- (Box-folder 42-53)
- Housing: Dining Xmas, 2003- (Box-folder 42-54)
- Continuing Education, Dining, Financial Aid, 2003- (Box-folder 42-55)
- Class Study Orientation, 2003- (Box-folder 42-56)
- Yakima/ H.E.P., 2003- (Box-folder 42-57)
- Yakima/ H.E.P., 2003- (Box-folder 42-58)
- Space Needle, Seattle Night, 2002- (Box-folder 42-59)
- Chemistry Teach, Fuel Cell, Flight Tech, Development Event, Science, 2003- (Box-folder 42-60)
- Headshots: Brooks Dedication, President Robinson, Trustees, 2004- (Box-folder 42-61)
- ABC's, Shell, Circuitboard, no date- (Box-folder 42-62)
- Studio Flower Shots Disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 42-63)
- Studio Flower Shots Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 42-64)
- 1892 diploma, no date- (Box-folder 42-65)
- Skies, Movement (conceptual), no date- (Box-folder 42-66)
- Variety: C.O.B. headshots, Rodeo, Chueh- Teaching, Zhao- Portraits, 2004- (Box-folder 42-67)
- Rodeo, Blox Concept, Campus Spring Sun, 2004- (Box-folder 42-68)
- Bonfire Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-69)
- Bill Board Finals, First Batch, no date- (Box-folder 42-70)
- Rez life: Heather Nicole Christian, Tom Christian, Mark Goodenberger, Liuxi Meng, Rabel, Sura Rath, Shimizu, Wildcat Welcome Weekend 03, Tom Conttrell, Hillary Thrift, Wenli Zhao, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 42-71)
- Central Today: Dan Jack, Forrest S., Fortune L., Higgins K., Manring C., Masden D., Melbourne T., Rittereiser S., 2004- (Box-folder 42-72)
- Lloyd's Prayer Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-73)
- Homecoming Football Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-74)
- Homecoming Football Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 4242-75)
- Lloyd's Prayer Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-76)
- C.O.B. Awards, 2004- (Box-folder 42-77)
- Flight Tech: Simulator, Meteorology Class, 2004- (Box-folder 42-78)
- Dining Mardi Gras, 2004 Housing: Room Sign Up (Box-folder 42-79)
- One World Taiko, 2004- (Box-folder 42-80)
- Seattle Symphony Music Building G.O., 2004- (Box-folder 42-81)
- Vagina Monologues, 2004- (Box-folder 42-82)
- Center Students, Housing Group RHA Group Shots, 2004- (Box-folder 42-83)
- Music Building: Architecture, Faculty, Students, 2004- (Box-folder 42-84)
- Math Class: Oursland, 2004- (Box-folder 42-85)
- Green House: Graduate Student Conducting Compost Research for Verhey, 2004- (Box-folder 42-86)
- Mark Goodenberger: percussion Professor, 2004- (Box-folder 42-87)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 42-88)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-89)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-90)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-91)
- Milo Smith Scrapbook Files 1-20, no date - (Box-folder 42-92)
- Views: Aerial, Fan Color, Garden, Japan Campus, Region, Bookstore, Snow, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 42-93)
- Rez Life, Habitat Images, no date - (Box-folder 42-94)
- Dining, 2003- (Box-folder 42-95)
- Nance Art: Paper People, no date- (Box-folder 42-96)
- Post ITS Graphic Shots Disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 42-97)
- Deep Sea Daze, 2004- (Box-folder 42-98)
- Variety 2: Flying Bridge (Science Building), Dale Hubbard Headshot, 2004 Orchestra Portrait with Cobb Conducting, Orientation 2003 shots for 2004 "Discover", 2003-2004 (Box-folder 42-99)
- Stock Disc 2: Carrier Quest 2004, Service Awards 2004, Music Construction 04/2004, Music Department Shots (Box-folder 42-100)
- Music Building Grand Opening Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-101)
- Music Building Grand Opening Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-102)
- Final Rez Life Corrected Images, 2004- (Box-folder 42-103)
- Mountain Bikers: Student Union Building Recreation Architecture Render, 2004- (Box-folder 42-104)
- Orientation Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-105)
- Orientation River Rafting 07/2004 Disc 1 (Box-folder 42-106)
- Orientation River Rafting 07/2004 Disc 2 (Box-folder 42-107)
- Orientation Disc 7, 2004- (Box-folder 42-108)
- Orientation Disc 6, 2004- (Box-folder 42-109)
- Orientation Disc 5, 2004- (Box-folder 42-110)
- Orientation Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 42-111)
- ROTC, Major Smith, 2004- (Box-folder 42-112)
- Building Bridges Scholarship Donor Honor Event, Service Awards Groups: 10 year, 15 year, 20 year, 25 year, 30 year, 35 year, 2004- (Box-folder 42-113)
- Welcome Back BBQ, 2004- (Box-folder 42-114)
- Centers: Lynnwood Pierce Disc 5, 2004- (Box-folder 42-115)
- Orientation Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-116)
- Fall Campus/Color Disc 5, 2004- (Box-folder 42-117)
- Braunstein, Physics, 2004- (Box-folder 42-118)
- Andrea Sledge, Teaching, 2004- (Box-folder 42-119)
- Jerilyn McIntyre: Teaching Disc 1 1-66, 2004- (Box-folder 42-120)
- Lori Sheeran, 2004- (Box-folder 42-121)
- Variety-1: Alumni merchandise, Art Class on lawn, Employees at Work, "Discover" Pee-Chee Faces, Diversity Group Portrait, International Group Photo, 1940's Kamola Girl's Photo, Lariviere Siblings as Kids, Observer Staff at Work, 2004- (Box-folder 42-122)
- Bonfire Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-123)
- Bonfire Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-124)
- Dining Events: Mardi Gras, Deep Sea Daze, Cinco De Mayo, 2004- (Box-folder 42-125)
- S.O.U.R.C.E., 2004- (Box-folder 42-126)
- R.H.A. groups: Mountain Bikers, 2004- (Box-folder 42-127)
- Ruth Lapsley Teaching, 2004- (Box-folder 42-128)
- Computer Science Classes, 2004- (Box-folder 42-129)
- Papadopoulos: Physical Education Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-130)
- Nethery Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-131)
- Nethery Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-132)
- Theater Variety: Milo Smith Scrap Book 21-28, Delondra Johnson, Summer Workshop, Smith Tower, 2003- (Box-folder 42-133)
- Orchestra, Cobb: Conducting, 2004- (Box-folder 42-134)
- Phil Backlund: Communication Class, 2004- (Box-folder 42-135)
- Nethery Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 42-136)
- Nethery Class Disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 42-137)
- Megan Matheson Disc 2 91-120, 2004- (Box-folder 42-138)
- Megan Matheson Disc 1: 1-90, 2004- (Box-folder 42-139)
- S.O.U.R.C.E., 2005- (Box-folder 42-140)
- RA's /IET CAMP: RA's north Campus Allyssa and Jeff, CAMP 2005 Group portrait, IET Final Images 2005 Brochure (Box-folder 42-141)
- Palmquist: Bruce Palmquist 11/2005, WA Professor Disc 2 (Box-folder 42-142)
- Palmquist: Bruce Palmquist 11/2005, WA Professor Disc 1 (Box-folder 42-143)
- Palmquist: Bruce Palmquist 11/2005, WA Professor Disc 3 (Box-folder 42-144)
- Des Moines Center Disc 2: Buildings, Interiors, Class, 2005- (Box-folder 42-145)
- Billboards Disc 12, 2005- (Box-folder 42-146)
- Billboards Disc 11, 2005- (Box-folder 42-147)
- Billboards Disc 10, 2005- (Box-folder 42-148)
- Billboards Disc 9, 2005- (Box-folder 42-149)
- Billboards Disc 8, 2005- (Box-folder 42-150)
- Billboards Disc 7, 2005- (Box-folder 42-151)
- Billboards Disc 6, 2005- (Box-folder 42-152)
- Billboards Disc 5, 2005- (Box-folder 42-153)
- Billboards Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 42-154)
- Billboards Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-155)
- Billboards Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-156)
- Billboards Disc 1: Pinkart with Student in Lab, Harbaugh with Students Playing Trumpets, Students Exiting Bus, Highline, Studio Shots: Dan Beck, Emily Washine, Zach Marquess, Mann Dempster, Cheree Carly Le, Amy Day, Ric Ibarra, 2005- (Box-folder 42-157)
- Amy Mumma at Winery Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-158)
- Amy Mumma at Winery Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-159)
- Mardi Gras Dinner, Nance bracken: Brush Steppe Painting, 2005- (Box-folder 42-160)
- SF Scottish Fiddlers, Career Quest, 2005- (Box-folder 42-161)
- Civic Engage Students: Round Table Conversational Shots, 2005- (Box-folder 42-162)
- Miscellaneous: Convention Group at McConnell, Empower Center Staff, Library and Students, Amy Mumma and Wine Images, 2005- (Box-folder 42-163)
- Student Appreciation Day Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-164)
- Fall Disc 1: Homecoming- Kamola, Alumni Events, Game, Wildfire; Fall Architecture, Color, 2005- (Box-folder 42-165)
- Miscellaneous 4 and 5 Retiree Headshots, Bridge Builders Awards, Linda Graf, Human Resources Award Groups, William Perry Lee Shapiro, 2005- (Box-folder 42-166)
- Student Appreciation Day Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-167)
- Miscellaneous Shots Disc 3: Campus Buildings, Diversity/ Non-tradition, Douglas H.C. Class, Housing Images Rez Haus, 2005- (Box-folder 42-168)
- Working Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-169)
- Working Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-170)
- Post IT Graphics Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 42-171)
- Miscellaneous: DE Class (GHOSH), Library comp Lab, Lombard 08/2005, Theater Faculty, Wellness Staff (Box-folder 42-172)
- C.O.B. Lynnwood: Students, Classrooms, Mike Ruble, Ozden Bayazit, 2005- (Box-folder 42-173)
- Tom Cottrell with Students: Flower, Biology Class in Field, 2005- (Box-folder 42-174)
- Miscellaneous Shots Disc 4: Dining Employees, Marching Band, Memorandum with Tribes 10/2004, Meghan Miller, Bob Trumpy Group Shot, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 42-175)
- Orchesis 2005: Dancer Headshots, Studio/Stage Dance (Box-folder 42-176)
- Miscellaneous Shots: David Abshire, Adam with Guitar, Fireside Chat 11/2004, Dean Nicholson Shots, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 42-177)
- CWU Sampler Images, 2005- (Box-folder 42-178)
- Central Connections Disc 2: Alumni Memorabilia, Alumni Photo Scans, Barkshire Race Driver, Cave B Shot, David Wain-Coon, Governor Gregoire at EDCC, Don May at NY/NBC, Amy Mumma, 2005- (Box-folder 42-179)
- Central Connections Disc 1: Marching Band Alumni Header, Keesler and Jones/Ottmar, Devlin Lombard Lamp, Mammoth Shots, Migrant Worker Shots, Shuford Plaque, Theater Montage, 2005- (Box-folder 42-180)
- C.O.B. Beacon Images: Sandy Wheeler, Kyle Boast-Basketball Shots, Katie Maurer, Ken Martin, Micah Powless, Business 2 Business Breakfast 02/2005, J.Delaney B2B 04/2005 Speaker, Lapsley Class, Denman (Box-folder 42-181)
- Commencement Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-182)
- Commencement Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-183)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-184)
- Student Union Building: Opening CR2's, no date- (Box-folder 42-185)
- Fall: Rally in the Alley, Civic Engagement, 2005- (Box-folder 42-186)
- Steven Nourse Photos: C.T.O.T. Program at WCCW, 2005- (Box-folder 42-187)
- Lasik Accounting Class, President's Cabinet Portrait, 2005- (Box-folder 42-188)
- College of Business: Fred McDonald Accounting Class, 2005- (Box-folder 42-189)
- Commencement Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-190)
- Commencement Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-191)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-192)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-193)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-194)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-195)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 42-196)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 5, 2005- (Box-folder 42-197)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 6, 2005- (Box-folder 42-198)
- Campus Spring: Valley Views Raw Files Disc 7, 2005- (Box-folder 42-199)
- Video Game Boxes Composition 01, no date- (Box-folder 42-200)
- Move-In Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-201)
- Move-In Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-202)
- Move-In Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-203)
- Move-In Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 42-204)
- Bite of the Burg Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-205)
- Bite of the Burg Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-206)
- Gear Up! Visiting 6th Grade from Prosser Washington, 2005- (Box-folder 42-207)
- Homecoming: Alumni Events Excellence in Teaching, Class of 1955, Lombard Ribbon Cut, Football Events, Car Bash, 2005- (Box-folder 42-208)
- Des Moines Grand Opening, 2005- (Box-folder 42-209)
- Des Moines Grand Opening, 2005- (Box-folder 42-210)
- Central Connection: Various Images, Duncan Bonjorni, 2005- (Box-folder 42-211)
- Miscellaneous Shots Disc 2: CHCI Building, historic Shots, Holmes Demo, Pat McCutchen, Men's Basketball, SAEM Webshots, 2005- (Box-folder 42-212)
- Des Moines Center Disc 1: Building, Interiors, Classes/Students, no date- (Box-folder 42-213)
- Spring Miscellaneous Campus Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-214)
- Spring Miscellaneous Campus Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-215)
- Road Trip Nation RV: Katrina Aid "Got Your Back" Relief Backpacks, 2005- (Box-folder 42-216)
- Variety: World Wine production Shots, Camp 2005 Group Shot, beacon 12/2005-Bayazit O, Neystedt AJ, Denman K, Jayne K, Soltz D, SSA Group, Various Scenes (Box-folder 42-217)
- C.O.B.: Advisory Board lunch and Meeting, 2005- (Box-folder 42-218)
- Accept Book Final Images Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-219)
- ROTC President's Review Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-220)
- ROTC President's Review Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-221)
- Libby Street: Teaching, 2005- (Box-folder 42-222)
- Highline CWU Des Moines, 2005- (Box-folder 42-223)
- Psychology Graduate Students, 2005- (Box-folder 42-224)
- Central Connections Disc 3: Duncan Bonjorni, Katrina Aid Meeting, 2005- (Box-folder 42-225)
- Katherine Whitcomb Writing Class, 2005- (Box-folder 42-226)
- Fisheye Campus Shots, 2005- (Box-folder 42-227)
- Stoddard Vessel Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-228)
- Stoddard Vessel Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-229)
- Stoddard Vessel Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-230)
- Lind Pendulum, 2005- (Box-folder 42-231)
- Migrant Worker last Light shots Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 42-232)
- Migrant Worker last Light shots Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 42-233)
- Migrant Worker last Light shots Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 42-234)
- Steve Douglas, Kevin Whitaker in SUB Construction, Bighorn Sheep in Canyon, 2005- (Box-folder 42-235)
- Library: Students Studying, 2005- (Box-folder 42-236)
- Fall: Campus/Color Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-237)
- Fall: Campus/Color Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-238)
- Fall: Campus/Color Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-239)
- Fall: Campus/Color Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 42-240)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-241)
- Commencement Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-242)
- Commencement Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-243)
- Commencement Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 42-244)
- Commencement Disc 5, 2004- (Box-folder 42-245)
- Commencement Disc 6, 2004- (Box-folder 42-246)
- Commencement Disc 7, 2004- (Box-folder 42-247)
- Commencement Disc 8, 2004- (Box-folder 42-248)
- Residence Life Disc 1: Heather Nicole Christian, Tom Cottrell, Liuxi Meng, Tricia Rabel, Sura Rath, Korri Shimizu, Hillary Thrift, 2004- (Box-folder 42-249)
- Back Up Disc 1: 2004 Housing Sign Up, Deep Sea Daze, Mardi Gras (Box-folder 42-250)
- Jerilyn McIntyre: Teaching Disc 2 67-131, 2004- (Box-folder 42-251)
- Pattie Loper Disc 2: 141-188, 2004- (Box-folder 42-252)
- Pattie Loper Disc 1: 1-140, 2004- (Box-folder 42-253)
- ROTC: Yakima Range Disc 2 151-275, 2004- (Box-folder 42-254)
- ROTC: Yakima Range Disc 1 1-150, 2004- (Box-folder 42-255)
- Pierce County Center: Grand Opening, 2004- (Box-folder 42-256)
- Pierce County Center: Grand Opening, 2004- (Box-folder 42-257)
- Accounting Class: Ron Tidd 80-100, 2004- (Box-folder 42-258)
- Centers: Yakima Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-259)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd, 2004- (Box-folder 42-260)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd 60-79, 2004- (Box-folder 42-261)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd 00-19, 2004- (Box-folder 42-262)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd 20-39, 2004- (Box-folder 42-263)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd 40-59, 2004- (Box-folder 42-264)
- Accounting Class Ron Tidd 100-120, 2004- (Box-folder 42-265)
- Billboard Shots: C.O.B. Beacon, 2004- (Box-folder 42-266)
- Terry Martin: Poetry Class, 2004- (Box-folder 42-267)
- Math Class: Stuart Boersma, 2004- (Box-folder 42-268)
- Centers: Pierce Disc 6, 2004- (Box-folder 42-269)
- Centers: Wenatchee Moses Lake SeaTac Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-270)
- Centers: Lynnwood Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 42-271)
- Centers: Lynnwood Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 42-272)
- Robert Carbaugh C.O.B Professor, 2004- (Box-folder 42-273)
- Gary Heesacker C.O.B. Professor, no date- (Box-folder 42-274)
- C.O.B. Advisory Board Meeting, 2004- (Box-folder 42-275)
- SUB Rec Ground Breaking, 2004- (Box-folder 42-276)
- Tartuffe Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-277)
- Tartuffe Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-278)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 42-279)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-280)
- Orchesis, 2004- (Box-folder 42-281)
- Stock Disc 1: Breckon- Extra Mile Award, Career Quest 2004, Tom Christian, Yvonne Cheh-Teaching, Michael Lariviere, Sally Lariviere, Michael Launius, Carmen Rahm, Michael Smith-Teaching Outdoors (Box-folder 42-282)
- Alumni Homecoming Shots Disc 2, 2014- (Box-folder 42-283)
- Alumni Homecoming Shots Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 42-284)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 3: Dieter Ullrich, Native American Students Shots, 2004 State of the University (Box-folder 42-285)
- Fall: Campus Color Disc 6, 2004- (Box-folder 42-286)
- Music Theater Fall: 2005- Working and The Foreigner, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 43-1)
- Central Theater Ensemble Peter Pan, 2008- (Box-folder 43-2)
- Postcard from L.A. Disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 43-3)
- Post Card from L.A. Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 43-4)
- Frankenstein Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 43-5)
- Theater: Concrete Dreams, Hay Fever, Jungle Book, Laramie Project, Macbeth, Pinocchio, West Side Story, 2003- (Box-folder 43-6)
- Tom Sawyer, 2006- (Box-folder 43-7)
- McConnell Twilight Theater: Disc 2 Spotlight Stage Shots, 2005- (Box-folder 43-8)
- Hard Times, 2006- (Box-folder 43-9)
- Fool of the World, Much Ado About Nothing, 2006- (Box-folder 43-10)
- Fool of the World Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-11)
- Fool of the World Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-12)
- Fool of the World Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 43-13)
- Aerials Looking East Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-14)
- Aerials Looking East Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-15)
- Aerials Looking West Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-16)
- Lombard Architecture Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-17)
- Lombard Hall, 2006- (Box-folder 43-18)
- Lind Hall Architecture Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-19)
- Lind hall Architecture Details Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-20)
- SURC Architecture/Detail Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-21)
- SURC Architecture/Concept Detail Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-22)
- CWU Buildings: Old S.U.B., Peterson Hall, Power Tech, Psych Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 43-23)
- CWU Buildings: Student Village, Wahle, Wilson, 2006- (Box-folder 43-24)
- CWU Downtown Architecture, Library Totem, 2007- (Box-folder 43-25)
- Wild Horse Wind Farm, 2007- (Box-folder 43-26)
- Wild Horse Wind Farm, 2007- (Box-folder 43-27)
- Al Monte, Carmody, Construction Zone, Music Building, 2008- (Box-folder 43-28)
- Dean EXT/INT Anthro Department Art from Farrell 01/2009 (Box-folder 43-29)
- Hill Hall Construction Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 43-30)
- Hill Hall Construction Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 43-31)
- Architecture, 2003- (Box-folder 43-32)
- Hill Hall, 2009- (Box-folder 43-33)
- Miscellaneous: Hogue Addition Construction, Ridge Trail Run with CWU Hummer, Spring Campus Malls, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 43-34)
- Region Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 43-35)
- Region Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 43-36)
- Architectural: Lynnwood Center, Health Center with Signage, 2011- (Box-folder 43-37)
- Barto Hall Construction Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 43-38)
- Barto Hall Construction Disc 2, 2012- (Box-folder 43-39)
- Looking West Aerials Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-40)
- Aerials Looking West Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 43-41)
- Aerials Looking West Disc 4, 2006- (Box-folder 43-42)
- Music Building Construction, 2003- (Box-folder 43-43)
- Music Building Construction Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-44)
- Music Building Construction Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-45)
- Shaw/Smyser with Barge and Big Sky, 2006- (Box-folder 43-46)
- SURC East Entry with Students, 2006- (Box-folder 43-47)
- SURC: Common Areas, All Meeting Rooms, Rock Wall, weight Room, Cardio Room, Pit, Smoothie Bar, Store Entrance, theatre, Ballroom, B.O.D. Offices, 2006- (Box-folder 43-48)
- SURC Rooms Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-49)
- SURC Rooms Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-50)
- Lombard Architecture Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-51)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 4, 2006- (Box-folder 43-52)
- Rounding Third, 2010- (Box-folder 43-53)